Yeah, go ahead. Uh CJ, welcome to
Indianapolis. Congrats on being drafted.
Um can you explain if the Colts any
contact with you throughout the
pre-draft process? And then secondly,
what you think it can bring to the NFL
team?
>> Uh we had a I have a formal with them.
Oh man, I'm sorry. There's going
>> Yeah, I had a formal meeting with them.
Um and I also had it came down to my pro
day and um and yeah, man. as far as I
can bring to the team, man. You you you
getting a dog. You getting you getting a
true linebacker that that can be able to
make your defense better, man. Run the
sideline to sideline. Really just love
football and just love defense, man. You
get a feel you get a physical linebacker
that can run
>> go ahead
>> CJ. What do you do best?
>> I I run and hit people best. That's
that's that's the best thing I do. Uh, I
think my my position just clarify what I
do as a linebacker, as an inside
linebacker, being able to run and hit
and get to that ball.
>> Jake, go ahead.
>> Hey, CJ. Uh, Georgia's got a storyried
history of these mic linebackers coming
into the league. You know, Rocoan Smith
is probably the most prominent example
of that right now. What does that mean
for you to be the next in line there?
>> It means a lot. I mean, I take it as a
badge of honor. I mean, that's what I
came to Georgia to do. That's what I
signed up for. I knew what I was signing
up for. And uh so just being able to get
the car to carry it on, just knowing
that I did it the right way, man. It
definitely means a lot. And to continue
that in the league and being built for
coach, man, it definitely mean a lot.
>> Abby.
>> Hi CJ. Congratulations. I also went to
Georgia, so go dogs. Um
>> go.
>> Um we know Kirby is very well known
across college football as a leader, one
of the best coaches in the league. What
are some of the best lessons you've
learned from him that you hope to uh
carry over with you into the league?
>> Really, uh, good is not good enough. I
mean, the the standard for us,
especially coming from Georgia, man, you
know, you're uh, man, excellent is a
good is the lowest bar you can beat.
But, man, the just the main thing of
him, man, nothing is given to you. You
know, you got you got to earn it. You
got to work. So, I just think those type
of things right there will forever just
be uh just something that's that's
instilled in me. also my character, you
know, um it's how I treat people, how I
talk people, being able to meet people,
and being able to meet with people, too.
>> Larara CJ, welcome to Indie. Just take
us through that anticipation
waiting to see where your NFL
destination would be and where you are,
who you're celebrating this with
tonight.
Um, it was definitely I'm sorry my
phone, but uh it was definitely uh it
was it was a little nerve-wracking, you
know, not knowing what's going on, not
know who's going to pick you, you know,
you know, you came down, you know, to to
a little man right there. So, man, um it
was definitely a little nerve-wracking,
but I knew, man, God timing is perfect
timing. But, man, I just, you know,
super excited to have my mom, my
sisters, my brothers next to me on the
couch and just surrounded by family,
surrounded by love. So, I know whichever
way it was go, you know, I still going
to be loved. So, it was very important
to me.
We'll do just a few more. Nathan,
>> hey CJ, congrats on the uh pick today.
Um question for you. This this Colts
team is um fairly thin at linebacker at
the moment coming into a team that has a
a big need for you. What what do you
know about or what's your impression of
the opportunity that you have here
coming to Indianapolis?
>> It means a lot, man. They chose the CJ
Allen, linebacker George. They just they
just say says the title right now what
they what they looking for and what they
want in the locker room team. So to me
that just means a lot to me right there.
So I'm coming to make the team better,
you know, get uh just be the guys, man.
I said make the team better. So it just
means a lot to me.
>> James,
>> one question I like to ask guys when
they get to this stage, what's your why?
Like you know, what is it about football
this game that you love so much or what
puts you in that mode to go out there
and compete?
Man, I just think the ultimate sacrifice
it requires you. I think it requires a
lot of sacrifice mentally and physically
that you wake up every day to do it. So,
I think that that that right there just
drive me, you know. I feel like I was
just born with born with some gifts. So,
man, I I want to be able to use my best
abilities and and exceed expectation. I
was my family. That's a big why to me
too. I do with my mom, my siblings, my
brother, you know, they've been here for
the start. So, just just supporting me
and also my community. My community
means a lot to me. The kids in my
community, they look up to me and I do
it for them, too.
>> We'll go with Kevin and then Jake will
be our last question.
>> DJ, did you um do the communication from
the sidelines? Were you the green dot
guy for Georgia?
>> Yes, I was a green dot. I was the green
dot in 20 this this previous year and
the year before that. So, my sophomore
and junior year.
>> Jake, last question. Yeah, CJ, with that
being the case, you know, being a rookie
coming in as the mic linebacker, the
green dot, if if you earn that as a
rookie, I mean, that's kind of a big
responsibility in a huddle with a bunch
of veterans. Like, how big is that to
you? Like, are do you find yourself
being a natural leader? Like, how does
that come to you?
>> Yeah, I definitely find myself being a a
natural leader that guys kind of gra
that gravitates toward to. I just think
about my freshman year coming in just
guys just respecting how the way I
worked and the way I showed up each and
every day. I think guys uh guys respect
those type of things. So man, I wouldn't
I would say it's a I don't look at it as
it's a big challenge. Okay, it's a big
opportunity and that and that will help
me to keep on